there should be no more electricity
we now have the solution here
once solar pennel
the summer comes out
Camping time is at the start
this solarpennel is now available at TikTok Shop
naturally wind and waterproof
everything no problem at all just set up
shows the Solar Panel stands
and of course we all have cables here already with us
integrated with it
yes perfect to connect everything these
energy center this box
which of course also comes with the big outputs
and All possible
we can charge up to 8 devices at the same time here
look
and solar pennel simply here into the energy center
infect and we see
how much input comes in here
just by the sunlight we have now
we have a 5758 volt input here right now
Sun pops in well
here we see the percentage how much
the powerbank or here the
energy center loaded is
energy-central of course
but also normal loading when we are at home
but right now we are just using the solarpenne
the solar pen is of course also compatible with other
uh energy centers and Co
that you want to use
so really very very simple
the whole as said water and dirt resistant
and now we charge the whole time n bit here